PROFESSOR: OK.
Let's do a quick quiz.
I'm going to pose a question to you and
give you some time to discuss with
those around you.
So imagine you have some
board like this.
This is a case where Pac-Man is
trying to eat all the dots.
There are some nasty ghosts
lurking about.
We are not going to think about this
as an adversarial search problem--
that will come later in the semester.
For now, think about the problem of
eating all of the dots in a kind of
safe way, where that ghosts
can't hurt you.
In particular, you have to keep that
ghosts kind of continually scared by
eating power pellets at
appropriate intervals.
So that's the problem-- eat all
the dots with the ghosts being
permascared.
And I'd like you to think about what
needs to go in your search state
representation.